dfwairport.com 2016-06-01

# dfwairport.com - Privacy Policy

|   
---  
|  |  |   
---  
  
dfwairport.com - Privacy Policy  |   
---  
  
The purpose of this statement is to tell you how DFW Airport may use the personally identifiable information that it collects from you when you use dfwairport.com. In addition, this is to advise you that, irrespective of any use to which DFW Airport may put such information, some of it may be subject to disclosure under the Texas Public Information Act, if it is requested.

COLLECTING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU  
DFW Airport is committed to helping its visitors experience at and through the Airport to be as smooth and hassle-free as possible. To aid in that commitment, you can visit and enjoy our website without disclosing any personal information about yourself. However, there may be times, such as when you purchase or order a product, subscribe to our e-newsletter, enter a contest or sign-up for our flight tracker service, at which we will ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, mailing/billing address, telephone number, e-mail address, license plate information, credit card information, birth date, gender, occupation, personal and/or travel interests, etc. BY PROVIDING THIS INFORMATION, YOU ARE GIVING DFW AIRPORT AND ITS AGENTS PERMISSION TO USE YOUR INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED HEREIN, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, TO OFFER YOU PRODUCTS AND SERVICES THAT MAY BEST MEET YOUR FUTURE NEEDS. DFW may also contact you to solicit your opinion on your current and future Airport experiences. Whether or not you choose to provide such information is completely your own choice, but if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our website.

USING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU  
We use the personally identifiable information you provide for purposes such as analyzing trends and statistics, monitoring parking activity, informing you of new services and offers and providing you with information about DFW Airport.  
We may contract with companies to provide certain services including credit card processing, data management promotional services, etc. In doing so, we may provide these companies with the information needed for them to perform the services requested by DFW. We require that these contractors make no other use of such information.

COOKIES  
To help us serve you better, we collect information that does not identify you personally, but rather identifies your computer or browser. This is done by using files called cookies and by tracking IP addresses. Cookies operate in the background and can be turned off if you wish. If you choose not to accept cookies, some pages or services on the site may not function properly.

DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION  
ALTHOUGH UNLIKELY, IN CERTAIN INSTANCES, WE MAY BE REQUIRED BY COURT ORDER OR SUBPOENA TO DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. MOREOVER, SOME OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, LIKE YOUR NAME, ADDRESS, PHONE NUMBER, GENDER, BIRTH DATE, OCCUPATION, PERSONAL AND/OR TRAVEL INTERESTS MAY BE SUBJECT TO DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES WHO REQUEST IT UNDER THE TEXAS PUBLIC INFORMATION ACT. WE MAY ALSO DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION TO ENFORCE OR APPLY OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS WEBSITE.

LINKS TO OTHER SITES  
OUR WEBSITE CONTAINS LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES OPERATED AND MAINTAINED BY THIRD PARTIES. DFW IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONTENT OR INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES OF THOSE SITES. WE ENCOURAGE YOU TO READ THE PRIVACY POLICY OF THE THIRD PARTY SITE WITH REGARDS TO ITS INFORMATION COLLECTION POLICY.

OPTING-OUT   
As mentioned above, DFW will occasionally send promotional material via e-mail or by other means. If you do not want to receive such promotional items, you can remove yourself from our e-mail list at anytime by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every e-mail.

COPYRIGHT NOTICE. Copyright 2003 The Dallas/Fort Worth International Airport Board U.S.A. All rights reserved. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.  
  
|
